

Ishita Agarwal Multimedia Journalist

My Contact

✓ Ishitaagarwal039@gmail.com

(8394031238

Business Point, Qila Rampur Road, Bareilly, U.P

My Portfolio

My Portfolio

🔚 LinkedIn Profile- Ishita_Agarwal

Hard Skills

- Content Writing (English & Hindi)
- Podcasting
- Typing (English & Hindi)
- Reporting
- Animation
- Anchoring

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Optimistic
- Hardworking

Education Background

- Invertis University
 - Bachelor's in Journalism and Mass communication Completed in 2022
- Girish Prasad Memorial College
 - Intermediate
 Completed in 2019
 - High School Completed in 2017

About Me

A bilingual multimedia journalist with a soul that is zealous and candour, driven by the intention to inspire with her work of bringing out breaking news plots and storytelling. Carrying with her, a prolonged experience in researching and crafting articles that resonate and cognizable, along with not lacking in information that keeps the people compelled. Also, expresses ability to produce innovative ideas to expand readership.

Professional Experience

Dainik Bhaskar | Sub Editor (Sports)

August 2024 - Present

Key responsibilities

- Working in the National newsroom of print as a sports journalist.
- Covering National and International Sports for print.
- Writing daily stories and co-ordinating with state level reporters.

Dainik Bhaskar | Fellowship

August 2023 - July 2024

Key responsibilities

- Collaborated with DB Digital newsroom (sports, national, international and eod desk).
- Worked as a Video producer for DB Digital.
- Helped in Reporting for Madhya Pradesh local team.
- Edited some articles of stringers team for Bhopal local.

Amar Ujala | Sports, Youth and Lifestyle Reporter

February 2022 - August 2023

Key responsibilities

- Specialised reporting of sports, youth and lifestyle.
- Researched and curated authentic information for news stories of daily happenings.
- Did Podcasting for Amar Ujala Awaaz.
- Organised events like Shatranj Mahotsav, Amar Ujala Open mic etc.

RocketTech | Social Media Manager / Content writer 3-month Internship (2020)

Key responsibilities

- Created and arranged daily content for Social media posting.
- Maintained engagement sheets and planned monthly strategies.
- Prepared reports of post engagement analysis and proposed improvements for better reach.

Achievements

2021- Winner in Advertisement making competition - *The Ad-Mad Show.*

2020-Published in the anthologies like Stardust and A Dreamer's Journal.

2022-Performed at Tape a Tale and Unerase Poetry.